drlam.com 2014-11-22

# www.DrLam.com Privacy Statement - DrLam® - Body. Mind. Nutrition®

www.DrLam.com Privacy Statement

Privacy Statement

This privacy policy was last updated Dec 1, 2008 

**Information Collection and Use  
**The [www.DrLam.com](http://www.drlam.com/) Web site collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site. When you use the Web site, some basic, general information is collected. This general information is used internally in connection with our business to improve the Web site, including our marketing and advertising efforts, and to make your use of the Web site as enjoyable and efficient as possible.

When you set up an account on our Web site or purchase goods and or services from our Web site, we collect personal information provided by you that may include your: (i) first and last name; (ii) billing address; (iii) shipping address; (iv) other shipping addresses; (v) email address; (vi) phone number; (vii) credit card account number; (viii) items purchased from us; and (ix) browsing, buying and selling patterns. We use this personal information in order to provide you with the goods and services that you purchase on our Web site. We use your email address to provide you with information about your order and its status and we may occasionally send out emails, including newsletters, to people who have placed an order on-line, with information about other goods and services available on our Web site. Your phone number is used by us only in the event that our customer service representatives need to contact you about an order you have placed.

Michael Lam, MD, ("we" or "us") owns and operates the [www.DrLam.com](http://www.drlam.com/) Web site and we are the sole owner of this information collected on the Web site.  We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities and may, in our sole discretion, disclose personal information or other information to satisfy any law, regulation, subpoena, or government request. We reserve the right to release personal information or other information about users who we believe are engaged in illegal activities or are otherwise in violation of our Terms of Service, even without a subpoena, warrant or court order, if we believe, in our sole discretion, that such disclosure is necessary or appropriate to operate our Web site or to protect the rights or property of [www.DrLam.com](http://www.drlam.com/), our affiliates, or our officers, directors, employees, agents, third-party content providers, suppliers, sponsors, or licensors. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities we reasonably believe in our sole discretion to be unlawful. If we are legally compelled to disclose information about you to a third party, we will attempt to notify you by sending an email to the email address in our records unless doing so would violate the law or unless you have not provided your email address to us.

**Registration  
**To use some features on the [www.DrLam.com](http://www.drlam.com/) Web site, a user must first complete a registration form on the Web site. During registration, a user is required to give contact information, such as name and email address. This information is used to contact users about the services on our Web site for which they have indicated interest.  In addition, certain  demographic information, such as age , height, weight, and gender are required if you wish to participate in certain services provided by the site. We encourage our users to provide such information so that we can provide a more personalized experience for our users on our Web site.

**Orders  
**We request additional personal information from our users when placing an order on our Web site for products or services. In completing our order form, a user must provide contact information, such as name and shipping address, and financial information, such as credit card account number , security validation code, and expiration date. This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill our customer orders. If we experience difficulties processing an order, we will contact a user through this information.

**Cookies  
**A cookie is a text file stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Web sites create cookies to record information about a user's preferences, such as the items you add to your shopping cart, and for security purposes (see _Security_ below). Cookies are also used to help us determine the various services you use and the support you may need, and to help us detect and solve any problems you may have while using our Web site. In addition, the use of a cookie on our Web site will enable users to log on without having to reenter their password on each visit and to fully participate in our Community discussions. Most cookies expire after a certain time period. If you wish, you may set your browser to reject all cookies and still view our Web site. Cookies placed by DrLam.com are not tied to any personally identifiable information.

Also, in the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

**Third Party Advertising  
**The ads appearing on this Web site may be delivered to you by us or third party providers. Information about your visits to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you.

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web sites, we may use log files on our servers. These log files store information regarding IP (internet protocol) addresses, browser type, ISP (internet service provider), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. These log files are used to analyze trends, administer the Web site, track user's movements in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for our use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personal information.

**Sharing of General or Demographic Information**  
We will share aggregated, general or demographic information we collect about our users and their use of our Web site with our partners (except where noted for specific co-branded relationships below) and advertisers in a manner which does not identify any individual user. We may use an outside shipping company to ship orders placed on our Web site, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services purchased on our Web site. These companies will not retain, share, store or use any of our user's personal information for any secondary purposes. We partner with other parties to provide specific services which are available on our Web site. When a user signs up for these services, we will share the user's name or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services to the use. These parties are not allowed to use such personal information except for the purpose of providing these services.

**Links  
**The Web site contains links to other Web sites. We want you to be aware that when you click on such links, including banner advertising, which take you to a third-party Web site, you will be subject to such third-party's privacy policies. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other Web sites and we expressly disclaim any and all liability for the actions of third-parties, including, without limitation, actions relating to the use and/or disclosure of personal information by such third-parties. We encourage our users to be aware of when they leave our Web site and enter a third-party Web site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects their personal information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by our Web site.

**Newsletters**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to one of our e-bulletins, e-alerts, either Dr. Lam.com’s Daily Tip or Weekly Newsletter, we will ask for contact information, such as name and email address.

**Send to a Friend**  
If a user elects to use our referral service to inform a friend about a part of our Web site, a form asks for the friend's name and email address. The form will automatically send the information to the friend via email. We may store this information for tracking and reporting purposes, and we will use the form only to send this one-time referral email.

**Public and Private Forums: Message Boards, Chats and "Ask Dr. Lam"**  
In order to post a message on our DrLam.com message boards or to the "Ask the Doctor" feature you will be asked to sign in with your member login information. We use this information in to recognize you for postings.  
With regard to the message boards, your email address is not visible on the boards however other users are able to send you email via your nickname without your email address being displayed. Dr.Lam.com generally does not share this information with any third parties unless required by authorized law enforcement agencies when required.

With regard to the "Ask Dr. Lam" feature, your name will be used if your question has been selected for use in the "Q & A" section of the Website. If you do not wish your name used, our Editors can, at their discretion, omit this information from the posted Q&A if you elect to remain anonymous and so request in the body of your submitted question.

Do remember that whatever you post on the message boards or use the "Ask the Doctor" feature, it is considered public knowledge and you should always use caution when posting. Avoid posting your home address or phone number on any public or private board or chat. Although one must be a registered user to post messages the message boards are public and may be read by non-registered users. Do not post any information you deem sensitive, personal, or confidential.

Dr.Lam.com reserves the right to re-publish your postings from the message boards in any format.

**Surveys and Contests  
**From time-to-time, our Web site requests information from our users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user has a choice whether or not to provide us with such information. Information requested may include contact information, such as name and shipping address, and demographic information, such as zip code, age level. Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used to monitor or improve the use and efficiency of this Web site. ****

**Security**  
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we may encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about the security of our Web site, you can send an email to _DrLam.com@gmail.com_

**Communications from our Web Site**  
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify their password and user name. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and the e-bulletins. Each user has the option to not receive these types of communications (see _Choice/Opt-Out_ below).

Occasionally, it is necessary to send out service-related announcements. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email informing you of such service interruption. Generally, users may not opt-out of receiving these service-related communications. In addition, we communicate with our users on a regular basis to provide requested services and regarding issues relating to their account via email.

**Correction/Updating Personal Information**  
If a user's personal information changes or if a user no longer desires our service, we will enable our users to correct, update or remove from our Web site the personal data they provided to us. Such changes can be made either through the member information page on our Web site or by emailing our Webmaster at DrLam.com@gmail.com.

**Choice/Opt-out**  
Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter, alerts etc  or other marketing and promotional materials from us or our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by clicking unsubscribe in each email.  
Users of our Web site will be notified if, in connection with the use of a particular service on our Web site, their information will be collected by any outside third-party. At such time, the user can determine whether they wish to proceed with a service that will involve an outside party having access to their information.

**Collecting Information From Children Younger Than 13**  
The [www.DrLam.com](http://www.drlam.com/) Web site does not knowingly collect or use any personal information from children under the age of 13 without obtaining verifiable parental consent. Drlam.com is open to users over 18 years old only.

**Notification of Changes in Use of Information**  
Our privacy policy is subject to change. In the event of any change, we will provide notice of such change on our Web site. If you have opted out of all communication with our Web site or have deleted or deactivated your account with us, then you will not be contacted and your personal information will not be used.  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or believe that the [www.DrLam.com](http://www.drlam.com/) Web site is not abiding by our privacy policy, please contact our Webmaster by e-mail at[ DrLam.com@gmail.com](mailto:DrLam.com@gmail.com)

Dr. Lam’s Adrenal Line

Dr. Lam’s Adrenal Daily Nutrient comes in powder form and allows you the ability to consume your daily fruit and vegetable intake along with necessary nutrients to help support your adrenals.  
This drink also acts as a complete multivitamin!
